Tufts-New England Medical Center Records MS224
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Financial records, 1969 -- 1981; MS224.004; 9.6 Linear Feet
  - 84780-2, Dr. Mintz, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.027.00002 (Box 27)
  - 84782-0, Nursing Home Improvement, Ms. Irey, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.027.00003 (Box 27)
  - 84784-0, Training Program on Aged, Ms. Frey, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.027.00004 (Box 27)
  - 84785-0, Ms. Frey, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.027.00005 (Box 27)
  - 84786-0, Education Facilities Lab, 1970; MS224.004.027.00006 (Box 27)
  - 84780-0, refund account, Mr. Doudera, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.027.00007 (Box 27)
  - 84790-0, preceptorship training, Dr. Jones, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.027.00008 (Box 27)
  - 84790-1, Preceptorship training, Dr. Jones, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.027.00009 (Box 27)
  - 84790-2, TUSM Preceptorship, Dr. Jones, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.027.00010 (Box 27)
  - 84791-0, Korda FDTN, Dr. Jones, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.027.00011 (Box 27)
  - 84795-0, Medex Education, Dr. Jacobs, 1974 -- 1976; MS224.004.027.00012 (Box 27)
  - 84796-0, Functional Task Analysis, Dr. Jacobs, 1974 -- 1976; MS224.004.027.00013 (Box 27)
  - 84797-0, Task activities analysis of emergency medical services, Department of Health Care Studies, 1974 -- 1977; MS224.004.027.00014 (Box 27)
  - 84805-0, T-NEMC Contingency Fund, MS224.004.027.00015 (Box 27)
  - 84810-0, Radiology Fund, Dr Kavanagh, Dr. Paul, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.027.00016 (Box 27)
  - 84820-0, Radiology Clinic, Inc., Dr. Ross, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.027.00017 (Box 27)
  - 84820-1, Radiology Clinic, Dr. Piro, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.027.00018 (Box 27)
  - 84820-2, Worcester City Hospital, Physics Contract, Mr. Thomas, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.004.027.00019 (Box 27)
  - 84830-0, Massachusetts Rehabilitation Engineering Clinic, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.027.00020 (Box 27)
  - 84830-1, Massachusetts Rehabilitation Engineering Clinic, Mr. Foulds, 1976; MS224.004.027.00021 (Box 27)
  - 84830-2, Massachusetts Rehabilitation Engineering Clinic, Mr. Foulds, 1977; MS224.004.027.00022 (Box 27)
  - 84840-1, Boston State Hospital (Anesthesia), 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.027.00023 (Box 27)
  - 84831-1, Massachusetts Rehabilitation Cardiac Rehabilitation, Mr. Hoskins, 1976; MS224.004.027.00024 (Box 27)
  - 84832-0, Massachusetts Rehabilitation Consumer Involvement Project, Dr. Fay-Pi, 1977; MS224.004.027.00025 (Box 27)
  - 84860-8, L.S.H. Diagnostic, Dr. Paul, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.027.00026 (Box 27)
  - 84860-9, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital - Diagnostic Radiology, Dr. Paul, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.027.00027 (Box 27)
  - 84861-0, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Surgery, Dr. Cleveland, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.027.00028 (Box 27)
  - 84870-5, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Therapeutic Radiology, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.027.00029 (Box 27)
  - 84910-5, Veterans Administration Hospital Diagnostic Radiology, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.027.00030 (Box 27)
  - 84910-6, Veterans Administration Hospital Diagnostic Radiology, Dr. Paul, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.027.00031 (Box 27)
  - 84910-7, Veterans Administration Hospital Diagnostic Radiology, Dr. Paul, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.027.00032 (Box 27)
  - 84910-8, Veterans Administration Hospital Diagnostic Radiology, Dr. Paul, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.027.00033 (Box 27)
  - 84920-5, Veterans Administration Hospital Therapeutic Radiology, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.027.00034 (Box 27)
  - 84860-5, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Diagnostic Radiology, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.028.00001 (Box 28)
  - 84860-6, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Diagnostic Radiology, 1975; MS224.004.028.00002 (Box 28)
  - 84860-7, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Diagnostic Radiology, 1976; MS224.004.028.00003 (Box 28)
  - 84850-5, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Anesthesia, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.028.00004 (Box 28)
  - 84850-6, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Anesthesia, 1975; MS224.004.028.00005 (Box 28)
  - 84850-7, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Anesthesia, 1976; MS224.004.028.00006 (Box 28)
  - 84850-8, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Anesthesia, Dr. Schmidt, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.028.00007 (Box 28)
  - 84850-9, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Anesthesia, Dr. Schmidt, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.028.00008 (Box 28)
  - 84851, Tufts Dental School Contract for Anesthesia Services, Dr. Schmidt, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.028.00009 (Box 28)
  - 84860-4, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Diagnostic Radiology, Mr. Cohen, 1973 -- 1974; MS224.004.028.00010 (Box 28)
  - 84870-7, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Therapeutic Radiology, 1976; MS224.004.028.00011 (Box 28)
  - 84870-8, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Therapeutic Radiology, Dr. Munzenrider, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.028.00012 (Box 28)
  - 84870-9, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Therapeutic Radiology, Dr. Piro, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.028.00013 (Box 28)
  - 84880-0, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Resident Services Contact, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.028.00014 (Box 28)
  - 84880-1, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Resident Services, 1975; MS224.004.028.00015 (Box 28)
  - 84880-2, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Resident Services, 1976; MS224.004.028.00016 (Box 28)
  - 84880-3, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Medical Residents, Mr. Kavanagh, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.028.00017 (Box 28)
  - 84880-4, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Medical Residents Administration, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.028.00018 (Box 28)
  - 84840-2, Boston State Hospital, 1975; MS224.004.028.00019 (Box 28)
  - 84850-4, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital, Anesthesia, 1973 -- 1974; MS224.004.028.00020 (Box 28)
  - 84920-6, Veterans Administration Hospital Therapuetic Radiology, Dr. Bloedorn, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.028.00021 (Box 28)
  - 84920-7, Veterans Administration Hospital Therapy, Dr. Munzenrider (Federal Medical Service Contract), 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.028.00022 (Box 28)
  - 84920-8, Vertans Administration Hospital Therapeutic Radiology, Dr. Piro, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.028.00023 (Box 28)
  - 84950-3, Chelsea Soldier's Home "Pathology", 1974 -- 1975; MS224.004.028.00024 (Box 28)
  - 84950-4, Chelsea Soldier's Home, Dr. Flax, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.004.028.00025 (Box 28)
  - 84950-5, Chelsea Soldier's Home, Dr. Flax, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.028.00026 (Box 28)
  - 84950-6, Chelsea Soldier's Home, Dr. Flax, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.028.00027 (Box 28)
  - 84870-6, Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Therapeutic Radiology, 1975; MS224.004.028.00028 (Box 28)
  - 84834-0, Pondville Hospital Medical Oncology, Dr. Wolff, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.004.028.00029 (Box 28)
  - 84832-1, Massachusetts Rehabilitation Commission CIP, Ms. Minch, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.028.00030 (Box 28)
  - ICCHS, Information Center Monthly Report III, 1978; MS224.004.028.00031 (Box 28)
  - Massachusetts Rehabilitation Commission Consumer Involvement Project Subcontracts, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.028.00032 (Box 28)
  - Clinical Education at the New England Medical Center Hospital: Analysis of Associated Health Professions Programs, 1977; MS224.004.047.00001; Ng, Mary L. (Box 47)
    Records of Research Accounting. Records of Associated Health Professions Education Project, 1976-1981
  - Allied Health Programs and Schools in New England, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.047.00002 (Box 47)
  - Program data sheets, 1973 -- 1980; MS224.004.047.00003 (Box 47)
  - Standard contract - implementation, 1979; MS224.004.047.00004 (Box 47)
  - The Future of Schools of Allied Health: Helping Schools of Allied Health Maintain Their Viability, 1974; MS224.004.047.00005; School of Health Studies - University of New Hampshire; American Society of Allied Health Professions (Box 47)
  - AHPED - Medical Technology Program proposal, 1978 -- 1980; MS224.004.047.00006 (Box 47)
  - NEMCH contract development, 1980; MS224.004.047.00007 (Box 47)
  - National Commission on Allied Health Education, 1976 -- 1978; MS224.004.047.00008 (Box 47)
  - Advisory Committee on Delivery of Health Services/Medical Foundation, 1978; MS224.004.047.00009 (Box 47)
  - National conference on civil rights of disabled citizens, 1980; MS224.004.047.00010 (Box 47)
  - National forum on allied health accreditation, 1979 -- 1980; MS224.004.047.00011 (Box 47)
  - Conference on human services coordination, Council of State Governments, 1980; MS224.004.047.00012 (Box 47)
  - Conference on breaking housing policy barriers to effective human services, 1980; MS224.004.047.00013 (Box 47)
  - Council on Postsecondary Accreditation, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.047.00014 (Box 47)
  - Legislation, 1977; MS224.004.047.00015 (Box 47)
  - Anderson, Ferguson, 1979; MS224.004.047.00016 (Box 47)
  - Clinical laboratory workers, personnel standards, 1979; MS224.004.047.00017 (Box 47)
  - Legislation, 1975 -- 1977; MS224.004.047.00018 (Box 47)
  - Department chairpersons, Tufts University, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.047.00019 (Box 47)
  - Administrative memos, 1979; MS224.004.047.00020 (Box 47)
  - Medline, 1977; MS224.004.047.00021 (Box 47)
  - Carrer patterns and mobility, 1973 -- 1977; MS224.004.047.00022 (Box 47)
  - Associated Health Project - presentation - Boston campus planning group, 1977; MS224.004.047.00023 (Box 47)
  - Tufts University Graduate School of Arts and Sciences catalogs, 1976 -- 1979; MS224.004.047.00024 (Box 47)
  - Hewison, Nancy, 1977; MS224.004.047.00025 (Box 47)
  - Tufts University Resources department, MS224.004.047.00026 (Box 47)
  - Notes on meeting of Committee on Public Health, 1977; MS224.004.047.00027 (Box 47)
  - Lazes, Peter, 1977; MS224.004.047.00028 (Box 47)
  - Lincoln Filene Center, 1977 -- 1979; MS224.004.047.00029 (Box 47)
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1977; MS224.004.047.00030 (Box 47)
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, Dr. Leo R. Sullivan, 1978; MS224.004.047.00031 (Box 47)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine clerkships listing of students, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.047.00032 (Box 47)
  - Tufts University medical school enrollment, student acceptance rate, 1977; MS224.004.047.00033 (Box 47)
  - Madoff, Morton, 1977; MS224.004.047.00034 (Box 47)
  - Primary care, 1977; MS224.004.047.00035 (Box 47)
  - Rehabilitation, 1977; MS224.004.047.00036 (Box 47)
  - Catalogue requests: Massachusetts colleges, re: Allied Health Programs, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.047.00037 (Box 47)
  - Tufts University biological sciences, 1977; MS224.004.047.00038 (Box 47)
  - Community health, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.004.047.00039 (Box 47)
  - Tufts University Engineering, 1976; MS224.004.047.00040 (Box 47)
  - Tufts University - general course information, 1977; MS224.004.047.00041 (Box 47)
  - Jackson College, 1977; MS224.004.047.00042 (Box 47)
  - Morgan memorial/Goodwill Industries, 1978; MS224.004.047.00043 (Box 47)
  - M&D library, Tufts University, 1970 -- 1980; MS224.004.047.00044 (Box 47)
  - Tufts University School of Veterinary Medicine, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.004.047.00045 (Box 47)
  - Occupational Therapy seminar, 1977; MS224.004.047.00046 (Box 47)
  - Letter to Dean Harleston, 1979; MS224.004.047.00047 (Box 47)
- Planning office records, 1932 -- 1985; 1960 -- 1975; MS224.005; 31.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains publications and administrative files of the T-NEMC Planning Office. The Planning Office records are divided into publications and administrative files. Publications consist of reports, authored by the Planning Office or outside agencies. Reports do not include a complete run of all publications. Also included in this series are survey data, architectural and engineering plans, budget projections, and files regarding urban planning in the South Cove neighborhood of Boston. Much of this material in this series was created by Hermann H. Field, the director of the Planning Office.
  - Planning library, 1957 -- 1985; MS224.005.001
    - Boston Floating Hospital Memorandum, #228, 1961; MS224.005.029.00001; Katz, Geneva (Box 29)
    - Report and Recommendations for Policies on Wages, Hours, Fringe Benefits and Personnel Practices in Hospitals, #376, 1959; MS224.005.029.00002; Katz, Geneva (Box 29)
    - Reports and Recommendations for Policies on Wages, Hours, Fringe Benefits and Personnel Practices in Twenty Massachusetts Hospitals, #377, 1960; MS224.005.029.00003; Katz, Geneva (Box 29)
    - Pediatrics and the Ambulatory Patient, #456, 1962; MS224.005.029.00004; Green, Morris (Box 29)
    - A New Design for Patient Care and Pediatric Education in a Children's Hospital: An Interim Report, #457, 1961; MS224.005.029.00005; Green, Morris (Box 29)
    - Study of the Facilities of the Boston Floating Hospital for Infants and Children Memorandum, #465, 1962; MS224.005.029.00006; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 29)
    - Elements of Projected T-NEMC, #554, 1963; MS224.005.029.00007; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 29)
    - Land Building Space Inventory, #657, 1962; MS224.005.029.00008; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 29)
    - Land Building Space Inventory, #658, 1962; MS224.005.029.00009; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 29)
    - Preliminary Projection and Existing Conditions According to Services and Medical Specialties, #4719, MS224.005.029.00010 (Box 29)
    - Meeting of Objectives Committee, #4720, 1961; MS224.005.029.00011 (Box 29)
    - Subjective Assessment of the Nursing Care at the New England Center Hospital, #4698, 1963; MS224.005.029.00012 (Box 29)
    - Information About Massachusetts Hospitals, #10108, MS224.005.029.00013; Massachusetts Hospital Association (Box 29)
    - Land Building Space Inventory, #10161, 1962; MS224.005.029.00014; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 29)
    - Annual and Progress Report, #10174, 1961 -- 1962; MS224.005.029.00015 (Box 29)
    - Summary and Excerpts from Doctors, Patients, and Health Insurance, #10191, 1963; MS224.005.029.00016; Harris, Anne S. (Box 29)
    - Architectural Dimension, #10194, 1963; MS224.005.029.00017; Field, Hermann H. (Box 29)
    - A Play Program and Its Function in a Pediatric Hospital, #10199, 1957; MS224.005.029.00018; Tisza, Veronica B.; Angoff, Kristine (Box 29)
    - A Proposal for a Dental Center of Tufts University, #10209, 1960; MS224.005.029.00019; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 29)
    - ABCD: Action for Boston Community Development, #10490, MS224.005.029.00020 (Box 29)
    - Boston: Three Centuries of Planning, #10492, 1964; MS224.005.029.00021; Eliot, Charles W.; Graham, Donald M.; Crane, David A. (Box 29)
    - General Itinerary, Tour of Urban Renewal and Development in Boston, #10493, MS224.005.029.00022 (Box 29)
    - School of Dental Medicine Pert Seminar, #10641, 1965; MS224.005.029.00023 (Box 29)
    - Submission to the Boston Redevelopment Authority, #10666, 1962; MS224.005.029.00024; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 29)
    - Summary: 1965/1975 General Plan for the City of Boston and the Regional Core, #10683, 1964; MS224.005.029.00025 (Box 29)
    - Project Improvement Report, #10742, 1964; MS224.005.029.00026; Hazen, Robert G. (Box 29)
    - Survey and Planning Application South Cove Urban Renewal Project, #10743, MS224.005.029.00027 (Box 29)
    - Urban Renewal Area Data, #10744, MS224.005.029.00028; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 29)
    - Progress Report 2, Health Sciences Centre, #10942, MS224.005.029.00029 (Box 29)
    - Progress Report 5, Health Sciences Centre, #10943, MS224.005.029.00030 (Box 29)
    - Progress Report 6, Health Sciences Centre, #10944, MS224.005.029.00031 (Box 29)
    - Progress Report 4, Health Sciences Centre, #10998, MS224.005.029.00032 (Box 29)
    - Report, #11059, MS224.005.029.00033 (Box 29)
    - Draft for Application for a Title III Operation Grant for the Quincy School Project, #11095, 1966; MS224.005.029.00034; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 29)
    - Tufts Medical-Dental Planning Committee Minutes and Agenda, #11107, 1965 -- 1966; MS224.005.030.00001 (Box 30)
    - T-NEMC Andover Planning Conference, #11109, 1968; MS224.005.030.00002 (Box 30)
    - NECH Inpatient Questionnaire Survey, #11132-11133, 1968; MS224.005.030.00003; King, Helen C. (Box 30)
    - People-Work Equipment Survey, #11161, 1963; MS224.005.030.00004 (Box 30)
    - Master Workbook B, #11163, 1963; MS224.005.030.00005; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 30)
    - Summer Program Notebook, #11165, 1963; MS224.005.030.00006 (Box 30)
    - Summer Study Surgery X-Ray, #11166, MS224.005.030.00007 (Box 30)
    - Hospital Planning, #11168, MS224.005.030.00008 (Box 30)
    - School of Dental Medicine Curriculum Study, #11169, 1965; MS224.005.030.00009 (Box 30)
    - T-NEMC Personnel Survey, Boston Dispensary Rehabilitation Institute, #11170, 1964; MS224.005.030.00010 (Box 30)
    - T-NEMC Personnel Survey, PC/NECH, #11171, 1964; MS224.005.030.00011 (Box 30)
    - T-NEMC Personnel Survey, BFH, Common Services, Dental School, Medical School, #11172, 1964; MS224.005.031.00001 (Box 31)
    - Dental School, Undergraduate Faculty Survey Material, #11173, 1965; MS224.005.031.00002 (Box 31)
    - Dental school program, #11174, 1963; MS224.005.031.00003 (Box 31)
    - Future medical center, #11175, 1963; MS224.005.031.00004 (Box 31)
    - Proposed site plan, #11176, 1980; MS224.005.031.00005 (Box 31)
    - Medical Schools and Teaching Hospitals: Curriculum, Programming and Planning, #11227, 1965; MS224.005.031.00006 (Box 31)
    - Preliminary Housing Market Analysis, #11230, 1961; MS224.005.031.00007; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 31)
    - The Health Fund for medical care, education, and research, #11231, MS224.005.031.00008; Vanderhoof, Albert W. (Box 31)
    - New England Medical Center Hospitals Industrial Engineering Report, #11239, 1967; MS224.005.031.00009; Chas. T. Main. Inc. (Box 31)
    - Minutes Recreational Facilities, #11282, 1966 -- 1969; MS224.005.031.00010 (Box 31)
    - Inpatient survey, #11289, 1967 -- 1969; MS224.005.031.00011 (Box 31)
    - Population Study: South Cove Project, 1965-1975, #11293, 1968; MS224.005.031.00012; Boston Redevelopment Authority (Box 31)
    - Coupling mental health services into the community general health system, #11294, 1967; MS224.005.031.00013; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 31)
    - Report on Recreation Facilities, #11301, 1967; MS224.005.031.00014; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 31)
    - Proposals For Recreation Facilities in the South Cove, #11304, 1967; MS224.005.031.00015; Boston Redevelopment Authority (Box 31)
    - T-NEMC Hospitals Mental Health Center Catchment Area Census Information, #11924, 1966; MS224.005.031.00016 (Box 31)
    - T-NEMC Patient-Visitor Survey Working Materials, #12045, 1962; MS224.005.031.00017 (Box 31)
    - T-NEMC Physical Facilities Questionnaires Working Materials: Supplement, #12047, 1962; MS224.005.031.00018 (Box 31)
    - T-NEMC Physical Facilities Questionnaires Summary Tabulations: Questionnaire Forms, #12048, 1962; MS224.005.031.00019 (Box 31)
    - T-NEMC Pedestrian Circulation Survey, #12051, 1962; MS224.005.031.00020 (Box 31)
    - Land Building Space Inventory, #12092, 1969; MS224.005.031.00021 (Box 31)
    - Applications of Computer Graphics in Community Mental Health Planning, #12670, 1969; MS224.005.031.00022; Hammer, William R.; Schmitt, Phyllis P. (Box 31)
    - Application for a grant of federal funds for construction of teaching facilities, #12748, 1969; MS224.005.032.00001 (Box 32)
    - Application for a grant of federal funds for construction of teaching facilities, #12804, 1969; MS224.005.032.00002 (Box 32)
    - The Medical School Program: A Preliminary Outline of Procedures, #12805, 1968; MS224.005.032.00003; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 32)
    - Summer Program Notebook, #12832, 1963; MS224.005.032.00004 (Box 32)
    - Application for a grant of federal funds for construction of teaching facilities, #12833, 1969; MS224.005.032.00005 (Box 32)
    - Application for a grant of federal funds for construction of teaching facilities - space description forms, #12834, 1969; MS224.005.032.00006 (Box 32)
    - Application for a grant of federal funds for construction of teaching facilities - space description forms, #12835, MS224.005.032.00007 (Box 32)
    - Addendum to application for a grant of federal funds for construction of teaching facilities - a narrative description including an architectural program with space schedules, #12838, 1968; MS224.005.032.00008 (Box 32)
    - Travel in Single Corridor Nursing Units Ranging from 1 to 84 Beds, #12860, 1970; MS224.005.032.00009; Lippert, Stanley (Box 32)
    - Barr & Barr Inc. Builders brochure, #12875, MS224.005.032.00010 (Box 32)
    - Dental, #12886, 1963 -- 1964; MS224.005.032.00011 (Box 32)
    - Application for project construction part I, #12909, 1970; MS224.005.032.00012 (Box 32)
    - Elements of Projected T-NEMC: Inpatient Direct Facilities, #12910, 1963; MS224.005.032.00013; Rupp, Maria E. (Box 32)
    - NEMC Hospitals Industrial Engineering Report Abstract, #12963, 1967; MS224.005.032.00014; Chas. T. Main. Inc. (Box 32)
    - NEMC Hospitals Industrial Engineering Study, #12965, 1967; MS224.005.032.00015; Chas. T. Main. Inc. (Box 32)
    - Pilot Health Care Program Terminal Report, #12987, 1967 -- 1970; MS224.005.032.00016; Gellis, Sydney S.; Field, Hermann H. (Box 32)
    - Library Subject Index, 1969 -- 1972; MS224.005.032.00017 (Box 32)
    - T-NEMC Planning Office Library Documents List (01-12,634), 1969; MS224.005.033.00001 (Box 33)
    - T-NEMC Planning Office Library Documents List (12,635-13,045), MS224.005.033.00002 (Box 33)
    - Proposals For Recreation Facilities in the South Cove, 1967; MS224.005.033.00003; Boston Redevelopment Authority (Box 33)
    - Report on Recreation Facilities, 1967; MS224.005.033.00004; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 33)
    - Problems of Pediatric Hospital Design, 1965; MS224.005.033.00005 (Box 33)
    - Inpatient Admission Questionnaire, MS224.005.033.00006 (Box 33)
    - Draft - Application for a grant of federal funds for construction of teaching facilities, 1970; MS224.005.033.00007 (Box 33)
    - A Report on the Construction of a Parking Facility at T-NEMC, 1969; MS224.005.033.00008; The Architects Collaborative Planning Office T-NEMC (Box 33)
    - Planning Committee Report Phase 1B, 1971; MS224.005.033.00009; T-NEMC Facilities Development Office (Box 33)
    - Fund allocation according to units of T-NEMC, 1965; MS224.005.033.00010 (Box 33)
    - Assessors Map, 1970 -- 1985; MS224.005.033.00011 (Box 33)
    - Sample schedules for inpatient survey (NEMCH), 1969; MS224.005.033.00012 (Box 33)
    - Sample schedules for T-NEMC housing survey, 1969; MS224.005.033.00013 (Box 33)
    - Sample schedules for recreation survey, 1969; MS224.005.033.00014; Hogg, Elizabeth (Box 33)
    - T-NEMC NEMC Hospitals Phase 1A, MS224.005.033.00015; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 33)
    - Application for a grant of federal funds for construction of teaching facilities, 1969; MS224.005.033.00016 (Box 33)
    - Memo: Site visit for November 1, 1969 renovations application, 1970; MS224.005.033.00017 (Box 33)
    - Administrative memorandum, 1969; MS224.005.033.00018 (Box 33)
    - Tufts School of Dental Medicine Building Committee meeting minutes, 1969; MS224.005.033.00019 (Box 33)
    - T-NEMC Andover Planning Conference, 1967; MS224.005.034.00001 (Box 34)
    - T-NEMC Andover Planning Conference, 1968; MS224.005.034.00002 (Box 34)
    - Architectural plans, MS224.005.034.00003 (Box 34)
    - Kubitz and Pepi contracts, 1972; MS224.005.034.00004 (Box 34)
    - Joint Planning Committee, Richard Viguers, 1967; MS224.005.034.00005 (Box 34)
    - Joint Planning meetings, 1968 -- 1969; MS224.005.034.00006 (Box 34)
    - Health Facilities Research Inc. proposal first draft, 1971; MS224.005.034.00007 (Box 34)
    - South Cove Project documents, 1965; MS224.005.034.00008 (Box 34)
    - Balance sheets, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.005.034.00009 (Box 34)
    - Dental Health Sciences building, 1967 -- 1969; MS224.005.034.00010 (Box 34)
    - T-NEMC Joint Planning Committee, 1966; MS224.005.034.00011 (Box 34)
    - Coonamessett Conference, 1970; MS224.005.034.00012 (Box 34)
    - T-NEMC Andover Planning Conference, 1968; MS224.005.035.00001 (Box 35)
    - Master Planning - Medical School Education Building Mash I Application Programming, 1969; MS224.005.035.00002 (Box 35)